{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Karl's term paper is inferior ___.",
      "a": "than mine",
      "b": "to me",
      "c": "to mine",
      "d": "than I",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Inferior to: not good, or not as good as someone or something else",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you read ___ of the story?",
      "a": "later half",
      "b": "the latter half",
      "c": "latter half",
      "d": "the later half",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- The story has the fist half and the second half. The latter half = second half.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Peter arrived in America ___ Jack did.",
      "a": "much later than",
      "b": "much latter than",
      "c": "as later than",
      "d": "very later than",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- The comparative form : Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n+ Structure: Adj (One syllable word) + er than; More + adj (Two-syllable words) + than ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "A good tale is ___ for being twice told.",
      "a": "none the worse",
      "b": "no worse",
      "c": "none worse",
      "d": "never worst",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- None the worse (for something): not damaged or hurt despite something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is none the ___ true because it sounds strange.",
      "a": "better",
      "b": "less",
      "c": "more",
      "d": "farther",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- None the less= however, nevertheless",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jessica was ___ most brave girl.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "so",
      "c": "far",
      "d": "one of",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- A most brave girl= a girl who is brave the most",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you think about Joe? \"He is wiser than ___ in his class.\"",
      "a": "any else ones",
      "b": "else any one",
      "c": "anyone else",
      "d": "any other one",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The comparative form: Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n- Anyone else: singular -&gt; the comparative form ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did you choose the lion as your symbol? \"Because he is considered the ___.",
      "a": "most nobility of beasts",
      "b": "noble beast of all",
      "c": "beast of all the most noble",
      "d": "noblest of beasts",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n+ Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; most+ adj (Two-syllable words) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Someone hit my car in the parking lot and didn't attempt to let me know. \" It seems that honest people are becoming ___ these days.\"",
      "a": "less and fewer",
      "b": "more and more",
      "c": "less and less",
      "d": "fewer and fewer",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Fewer and fewer: keep decreasing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "If the teacher's life is hard, the doctor's is even ___.",
      "a": "harder",
      "b": "more hard",
      "c": "the hardest",
      "d": "more hardly",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- The comparative form : Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n+ Structure: Adj (One syllable word) + er than; More + adj (Two-syllable words) + than \n- Hard -&gt; harder",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}